[
  {
    "itemName": "cm_1",
    "roiFront": "217,133,115,43",
    "roiBack": "217,133,115,43",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_2",
    "roiFront": "333,135,92,44",
    "roiBack": "333,135,92,44",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_3",
    "roiFront": "554,135,113,40",
    "roiBack": "554,135,113,40",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_4",
    "roiFront": "667,136,94,41",
    "roiBack": "667,136,94,41",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_5",
    "roiFront": "889,133,112,44",
    "roiBack": "889,133,112,44",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_6",
    "roiFront": "1002,133,91,42",
    "roiBack": "1002,133,91,42",
    "mode": "Single",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_number",
    "roiFront": "1105,564,60,28",
    "roiBack": "1105,564,60,28",
    "mode": "DigitCounter",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "记录已完成的数量"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_1_matter",
    "roiFront": "427,172,100,27",
    "roiBack": "427,172,100,27",
    "mode": "DigitCounter",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "材料的数量"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_2_matter",
    "roiFront": "429,293,100,31",
    "roiBack": "429,293,100,31",
    "mode": "DigitCounter",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_3_matter",
    "roiFront": "428,416,100,29",
    "roiBack": "428,416,100,29",
    "mode": "DigitCounter",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "cm_4_matter",
    "roiFront": "430,536,100,33",
    "roiBack": "430,536,100,33",
    "mode": "DigitCounter",
    "method": "Default",
    "keyword": "",
    "description": "Ocr-description"
  }
]